foreign
okay so we have the same exact deck in
the same exact order so your top two
cards should be ten of clovers and king
of Black Tears I have clubs I guess you
say clubs I say clovers tomatoes and
then uh king of Black Tears what's that
you mean the Spade with the spade a
spade like it's like this shape yeah it
looks like a black tear or a Hershey
Kiss somebody's nose that is
weirdly accurate let's deal it out baby
okay I hope we did it right do the king
of black tears and I have the Jokers I
took all the Jokers out of my deck
that's just a rule of my family because
those are like wilds and no I have the
Ten of clubs what's clubs clovers right
to my day to my Day weekend
Oh wait who's this
Tim Curry Nanny McPhee
can we just play Solitaire individually
and just talk they can only play
Solitaire online oh because it'll like
yeah
yeah you just acting out like what that
makes you feel like don't be mad dude
but I just I'm just sitting here with my
vibrator I'm not vibrating it's not
inserted we've had this conversation
before about how I would like to know
when that was going on I'm not building
up to something this is not does not
have a narrative to it it's the same as
if I had a heating pad I have a heating
pad on the small of my back right now
well you're also a pervert I think we
need a second to think about this
okay I'm really sorry I betrayed your
trust it's all right I'll text you in
like a little bit
all right bye bye McPhee
[Music]